Hello friends, let's discuss today's long part,
let's see here that the company has
declared its quarterly earnings at ₹7 per share,
whose ratio is 70%. Talking about the company's revenue, the
company earned a gross premium of Rs
64747 lakh in the last quarter. The company earned a premium of Rs
626312 lakh last year. The company has
earned a premium of Rs 6,90,394 lakh in this quarter.  The company
's gross premium is increasing year after year and
quarter after quarter.
Talking about the net premium of the company, the
company had
earned a net premium of Rs 5865 lakh in the last quarter.  The company has
earned a net premium of Rs 476716 lakh last year.   The
company earned a net premium of Rs 5,481.03 lakh in this quarter.  The
company's net
premium is increasing year after year and quarter after
quarter.
Talking about the total earnings of the company, the total earnings of the company in the
last quarter was Rs 588 lakh.  The
total earnings of the company last year were Rs 516
lakh.  The total earnings of the company
in this quarter was Rs 585 lakh.  The
company's total earnings are increasing year after year.
But a
decline is being seen quarter after quarter.
Talking about the company's expenses, the company had
spent Rs 140 lakh in the last quarter.  The
company had spent Rs 9 lakh last year.  The
company has
spent Rs 731 lakh in this quarter.  Looking at the company's expenses, the
company is seeing growth quarter after quarter
and year after year.
Talking about the company's profit, the company had made a
profit of Rs 72 lakh in the last quarter.  The company had made a
profit of Rs 51 lakh last year.  The company has made a
profit of Rs 50 lakh in this quarter.   The
company's profits are declining year after year and
quarter after quarter.
Talking about the company's EPS, the
company's EPS was ₹14.48 in the last quarter.  The
company's IPS was ₹10.47 last year.   The
company's IPS was ₹10.20 in this quarter.  The
company's APs are seeing a decline year after year and
quarter after quarter.  That's all for
today's video.   If you like the
video, please like, share,
comment, subscribe to the channel and
consult your personal advisor before investing.  Thank you.